http://www.800poconos.com/privacy-policy/

x
Alert
Before traveling, call your destination for any changes. Masks are mandatory indoors & outdoors even if you’re socially distant. Out of state visitors are required to get tested within 72 hours before entering PA. PA residents who travel to other states must follow same rules when returning.
Learn More
Meetings
Meetings
Submit an RFP
Meeting Facilities
Meeting Facilities
Hotels
Resorts
Interactive Map
The site uses cookies to store information on your computer. Some are essential to make our site work, others help us improve the user experience. By using the site, you consent to the placement of these cookies.
Read our Privacy Policy to learn more.
Accept & Dismiss
Privacy Policy
The Pocono Mountains Visitors Bureau respects your privacy. We are committed to protecting your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains the types of personal information we collect through our website, www.poconomountains.com, how we use and keep that personal information safe and how you can view and update it.
If you provide us personal information through the Pocono Mountains website, you can request that we not contact you in the future or share your personal information with any other organization. If you give us permission to contact you in the future, the Pocono Mountains Visitors Bureau, hereinafter referred to as ‘PMVB’, Pocono Tourism organizations and businesses may provide you with current and future information about travel opportunities in the Pocono Mountains.
Topics
How to Contact the PMVB
Contact Information
What Information Do We Collect About You?
Content and Information Disclaimer
Collection and Use of Personal Information
Collection and Use of Non-personal Information
Cookie Policy
Social Media Disclaimer
Automated Decision Making and Profiling Disclaimer
How Do We Use Your Information?
Use of Information
How Do We Protect Your Information?
Protection of Personal Information
Photo & Video Release
Reviewing/Updating Your Information
Agreement
How to Contact the PMVB
Contact Information
1004 W. Main Street
Stroudsburg, PA 18360
1-800-POCONOS (1-800-762-6667)
For questions about privacy and data collection through www.poconomountains.com, contact pocomts@poconos.org.
What Information Do We Collect About You?
Content and Information Disclaimer
Information on this site, is carefully compiled to ensure accuracy. At certain places on this PMVB website, live links to other Internet addresses can be accessed. Such external Internet addresses contain information created, published, maintained or otherwise posted by third-party institutions or organizations independent of the PMVB. The PMVB does not endorse, approve, certify or control these external Internet addresses and does not guarantee the accuracy, completeness, efficacy, timeliness or correct sequencing of information located at such addresses. Use of any information obtained from such addresses is voluntary and reliance on it should only be undertaken after an independent review of its accuracy, completeness, efficacy and timeliness. Reference therein to any specific commercial product, process or service by trade time, trademark, service mark manufacturer or otherwise does not constitute or imply endorsement, recommendation or favoring by the PMVB. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the information collection processes on these sites and cannot control how the information is used. Please view the privacy policies on these third-party websites for more information.
Collection and Use of Personal Information
The PMVB does not collect any personal information through www.poconomountains.com except that knowingly and willingly supplied by the user for the purpose of providing the services/information requested through our site. We will collect personal identification information from users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Personal identifying information may be collected through e-newsletter forms, online request forms, contests, feedback forms, surveys and personal interest forms. Any information that the user provides, such as name, address, email, ZIP code, age, gender and income will be stored in a secure location and will be used only for those purposes stated.
When you choose to submit such personal information, you are transferring that information into the United States of America and are consenting to such transfer. All data transferred will be/is encrypted (Hypertext Transfer Protocol Secure, or HTTPS) transfer, through Secure Sockets Layer or SSL. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, noting that choosing to do so may prevent the user from engaging in certain site-related activities. Users of our services, such as e-newsletter subscriptions, may also withdraw consent for the use of their personal information at any time. To review, update or delete your collected data or to withdraw consent for use, contact pocomts@poconos.org.
While on the PMVB website you may voluntarily choose to be added to PMVB email lists. When you choose that option, the PMVB places you on lists to receive information about Pocono Mountains attractions, events and/or accommodations of general interest to individuals who live in or visit the Pocono Mountains. You may at any time update your profile and/or remove yourself from this email list from an unsubscribe link located at the bottom of every email.
Collection and Use of Non-personal Information
We may collect non-personal identification information about users whenever they interact with our website. We collect the domain name from each site visitor as well as statistical information, such as the number of visitors and the pages viewed. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer being used and technical information about the user’s means of connection to our site, such as the operating system, IP address and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. The information we collect is used to enhance the usability and improve the content of our web pages. It may be used to personalize information and for statistical purposes.
Cookie Policy
A cookie is a small text file that the website asks your browser to store on your computer or mobile device for record-keeping purposes. This information is taken from the computer's web browser and may include your IP address, operating system, browser, screen resolution and previous website.
This website utilizes cookies to gather visitor data for advertising on third-party websites (including Google and Bing) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who have not completed a task on our site or visited key pages, for example requesting a brochure. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Pocono Mountains website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy, Google’s privacy policy and other third-party vendor privacy policies. You can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting Google's Ads Settings. Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page.
Social Media Disclaimer
The PMVB promotes through a series of Pocono Tourism social media channels, @PoconoTourism.  Pocono Tourism has contests in which you may voluntarily enter your personal information to be eligible for a chance to win. In entering our social contest, your personal information will be added to our consumer database and you will receive our e-newsletters. You will receive an opt-in email beforehand to confirm your subscription. You can unsubscribe directly from this opt-in email, or at any time in the future by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of every email newsletter.
Our website includes social media programs and features, such as PMVB User Generated Content powered by Visiotopic, Facebook Ads and applications; the Facebook Like button and widgets and the Share button. If you choose to use these features, they may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. The social media programs, features and widgets we use are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the feature(s).
Automated Decision Making and Profiling Disclaimer
The PMVB works with third-party companies that utilize automated decision-making processes, including user profiling and location-based pixels, to provide more relevant marketing material to those users who opt-in to receiving emails from us.
How Do We Use Your Information?
Use of Information
Personal information will not be shared with third-parties unless indicated and when approved by the user, if the user opts-in to sharing information or unless required to do so by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, court orders, legal process from law enforcement agencies or similar legal proceedings. We provide information to investigate or prevent suspected illegal activities, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request, in certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements and to a third-party with your prior consent to do so.
The PMVB will retain personal data we process until the visitor/user notifies us that he/she no longer wishes to receive the services or information for which the data was collected. The PMVB will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.
How Do We Protect Your Information?
Protection of Personal Information
The PMVB supports the development and operation of partner services/products that interact with client user information. We request that our partners meet industry standards for security data storage and maintenance equivalent to those that we uphold or higher regarding any data collected by our partners or by the PMVB in conjunction with these partner services/products. Where applicable, we enter into binding agreements ensuring all parties meet minimum data security standards.
We acknowledge that we may face liability in cases where there is an onward transfer of your personal information from us to a third-party. We hold those third-parties with whom we do business to the same rigorous security standards that we impose on ourselves.
The PMVB employs processes intended to protect user information and maintain security of data. We seek to protect our servers by locating them in areas with documented security procedures, by using firewalls and by implementing other security technologies. These safeguards help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of data. However, despite our preventative measures and those of our partners, no guarantee can be made that your information and data will be secure from intrusions and unauthorized release to third-parties.
Photo & Video Release
By using the hashtag #YesPMVB or responding with yes or other affirmative statements when asked if PMVB may use one of your photos or videos, you hereby acknowledge that your media may be selected for use on Pocono Mountains Visitors Bureau’s, hereinafter referred to as “PMVB,” social media channels or marketing materials including advertisements or other company publications. PMVB retains the right to continue or discontinue use of  photos or videos at its discretion. PMVB is not obliged to use every photo or video supplied through the #YesPMVB hashtag. Click here for full release.
Reviewing/Updating Your Information
You have the right to review your information at any time. If you would like to review your information within our contacts database, update it, or remove it, please contact pocomts@poconos.org.
If you would like to be removed from or change your subscriptions to any of our newsletters, there is a link at the bottom of every newsletter that allows you to do so.
Agreement
By using this website, you agree to our Internet Privacy and Usage Policy and to the use of the information we receive and collect as stated herein and in ways we may notify you of in the future. By providing any personal information to this site, you acknowledge that you fully understand and consent to the collection and processing of such information. Your continued use of this site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes. See this quick download for a copy of this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right at our discretion to change and update our privacy policy at any time. Any changes to our policy will be posted on this site. Last updated: 6/25/2018
Back to Top
Pocono Mountains Visitors Bureau
Official destination marketing organization for Carbon, Monroe, Pike, and Wayne Counties, PA – collectively known as the Pocono Mountains
1004 W. Main St. Stroudsburg, PA 18360 | 570-844-2001 | pocomts@poconos.org | PoconoMountains.com
